That's everything
I've ever wanted in a friend.
(Raj:)Yeah, but if he's a sore loser,
maybe you're better off without him.
(Sheldon:)You're right.
(Sheldon:)I guess I just have to make lemonade
out of the two of you.
Ah! He played. He played.
(Sheldon:)Coop and Rolling Thunder
are together again.
(Sheldon:)He was okay with that nickname.
- So now all you have to do is let him win.
- Yeah, way ahead of you.
I will play the word "at"
for two measly points...
(Sheldon:)...throwing the game
and thus securing my friendship...
(Sheldon:)...with the smartest man in the world.
(Howard:)What are you waiting for? Hit send.
(Sheldon:)I can't. Losing on purpose
is intellectually dishonest.
- So don't do it.
- Oh, but I wanna be Hawking's friend.
- So do it.
- But if I do, I'll be a phony.
(Sheldon:)A sellout. A Hollywood poser.